Andrew Anc Jr.

andrewancjr@gmail.com • (978) 457-5782 • Hampstead, NH. github.com/aancjr/ • linkedin.com/in/andrew-anc-0911721a/

Summary Statement

Experienced React.js and front-end Software Developer with additional familiarity in back-end software languages. Success has been built by working closely with stakeholders, management and team to develop enhancements and resolve defects, increase visibility into company data through web-based interfaces, and work closely with teammates to accurately prioritize work through each program iteration.

Skills

• Regular Usage: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React.js, SQL, REST API, GIT

• Familiar With: node.js, NPM

Work Experience

Software Developer - EBSCO Industries, Ipswich, MA

March 2020-Present

- Actively creating, enhancing and refactoring internal tools to improve the day to day for employees, while giving deeper and more relevant insight into customer data
- Created a Customer Dashboard to help all of Sales, Project Management and Tech Support quickly view and digest crucial customer information, saving time in the customer research process
- Created a Current Order Customer tool allowing all of Sales to search for customers who have 'x' product(s) but do not have 'x' product(s), allowing them to easily prospect and upsell/cross sell into their territories
- Efficiently and effectively communicate with stakeholders to provide the MVP within the time specified. Identify enhancements and potential issues prior/during work and prioritize tasks for completion
- Collaborate with the team to plan and identify needs for planned work, creatively solve problems, identify future solutions
 and utilities, and provide valuable assistance. Execute and implement code based on iteration work following Agile
 principles, white tracking work through Rally
- Participate in regularly scheduled stand-ups and retro's to give team members insight into current work and assist others in their work

Account Executive - EBSCO Industries, Ipswich, MA

Nov 2013 - March 2020

- Research and identify customers with ideal fit to products. Educate and work closely with clients to implement and build brand awareness and recognition
- Collaborate with team members to strategically increase revenue, enhance brand availability and retain customers

Dealer Relations Manager - CarGurus, Inc., Cambridge, MA

July 2018 - December 2018

• Maintain customer relationships and increase revenue, while increasing software knowledge with multiple account contacts

Education

Web Development Bootcamp - University of New Hampshire, Durham, NH

March 2019 - September 2019

- Primary Tech Stack: MERN.
- Relevant Languages and Concepts: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery, React.js, SQL, REST API, Git.

Bachelor's of Science in Business - Full Sail University, Winter Park, FL

March 2009 - September 2011